<resources>
    <string name="app_name">WA Story Saver</string>

    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="image">IMAGES</string>
    <string name="video">VIDEOS</string>
    <string name="save">SAVED FILES</string>
    <string name="no_files_found">No Files Found</string>
    <string name="cant_find_whatsapp_dir">Cannot Find Whatsapp directory</string>
    <string name="allow_permission">allow permission</string>
    <string name="please_allow_permission">Please allow permission</string>
    <string name="exit">Exit</string>
    <string name="allow">allow</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy">mynotepad app priacy policy My Notepad Inc. Privacy Policy [Last Updated: 10/06/2022]

Protecting your privacy is an important aspect to My Notepad Inc. With this in mind we are providing this “Privacy Policy” to explain our practices regarding the collection, processing, use and disclosure of information store in the App.

Revision to this Privacy Policy Any information collected via our service is governed by the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is collected. We may revise this Privacy Policy from time to time. In case any material changes are made to this Privacy Policy, we’ll notify you those changes by either posting, emailing them or other notification. We’ll update the “Last Updated” date above to indicate when those changes will become effective.

Collection of Information None of your personal information will be collected. This includes individual identifiable information, information that identifies or may with reasonable effort identify an individual.

Information that we Share with Third parties We will not share your personal information collected by us

Links to Other sites Our Service may contain links to websites and services that are owned or operated by third parties. Any information that you provide on or to a Third-party or that is collected by a Third-party Service is provided directly to the owner or operator of the Third-party Service and is subject to the owner’s or operator’s privacy policy. We re not responsible for the content, privacy or security practices of any Third-party Service. To protect your information, we recommend that you carefully review the privacy policy of all Third-party services that you access.</string>

</resources>